So let me show you another one another way to dump and it's a process in previous video
we have used a rock dump to dump Ls in this video we are using the nano dump T axis to
dump an Ls as you can get a nano dump from this 4 crown nano dump block my Indist nano
dump.exe directory from a GitHub so let's download once you download the nano dump it's
an easy command you need to just execute the nano dump in this nano nano dump.exe and
our right will be the writing the Ls dump inside the termed our repository so you can choose
which which folder or directory or repository whatever you can say if you want to choose
I was choosing the C term Ls as C term Ls.dum directory let me execute this so this
the third is also one of the thing the that was commonly used by the detectors to dump an
Ls from the targeted machine so we have seen this nano dump was involved in lot of
incidents in lot of time whenever we dealing with the active incidents okay so now the
dump has been created and we know the size of the dump is more than 10 MB and it's
the dump for a successful as of now we yeah that's all about this video we got a dump
and yeah we hope of and we'll connect you in our next video thank you guys bye